[Music]
I'm a workaholic and sometimes it's good, sometimes
not so much
Mrs. Gangwani Sara's momma People don't
call me Simran anymore It started as a
hobby in summer vacation But between studies and school
I totally lost touch The house is big
and now there are fewer people living there Toh the house feels empty
Well, I have really had a hard time working As it took a
toll on my life and especially my health I
decided one date change was required I had to put myself first before anything else At
home, managing everyone's routine
is my routine So I
awakened the Simran in me once again And I joined
online yoga classes And there everyone
calls me Simran I started it to pass time
And now I have made new friends So I feel
really lonely So why not
try out new things to old new
things It hurts in the beginning I was
not used to it at all But you know I have heard that
if you do something continuously for 21 days then it becomes difficult
Habits grow and become habits Now if I do
n't practice for a day, I feel incomplete I
think karate has brought a balance
in my life which was not there at all before
Everyone's routine at home is still the same But
mine is a little different I feel the change and I
think I'm getting my age
[music]
back